Register of the Ivan Alekseevich Kurganov Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- WRITINGS BY OTHERS, 1917-1974
  - Mel'gunov, Sergei P., 1917-1948 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Pegov, G., 1952 (Folder 22: 7)
  - Perov, Pavel, 1970 (Folder 22: 8)
  - Poremskii, V., 1968 (Folder 22: 9)
  - Pushkarev, Sergei, 1967-1970 (Folder 22: 10)
  - Rutich, N., 1960 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Saaruni, Grigor, 1951 (Folder 23: 2)
  - Samarin, Vladimir, 1968-1974 (Folder 23: 3-4)
  - Sorokin, Pitirim, 1959-1961 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Srechinskii, Iu., 1974 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Stepun, Fedor, 1962 (Folder 23: 7)
  - Troitskii, Nikolai, 1972-1973 (Folder 23: 8)
  - Ul'ianov, N., 1972 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Vysheslavtsev, B. P., 1957 (Folder 24: 2)
- CLIPPINGS, 1953-1980
  - General
    - 1977-1979 (Folder 24: 3)
    - 1979 (Folder 24: 4)
    - 1980 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Akademiia nauk SSSR, SEE Scientists
  - American Committee for the Liberation of the Peoples of Russia, 1961 (Folder 24: 6)
  - Authors, Soviet
    - 1962-1968 (Folder 24: 7)
    - 1970-1974 (Folder 24: 8)
  - Citizenship
    - Soviet Union, 1979 (Folder 24: 9)
    - United States of America, 1957-1980 (Folder 24: 10)
  - Intellectuals (Folder 24: 11)
    - Europe, Eastern - Political activity, 1967-1969
    - Soviet Union., See also Europe, Eastern (Box 25)
      - 1949-1974 (Folder 25: 1-2)
      - 1968 (Folder 25: 3-4)
      - 1969-1970 (Folder 25: 5-7)
    - 1969-1970 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Russians in foreign countries
    - 1957-1958 (Folder 26: 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Folder 26: 3)
  - Scientists - Soviet Union and Akademiia nauk SSSR - Membership, 1962-1968 (Folder 26: 4)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Soviet Union, 1966-1968 (Folder 27: 2)
- CARD FILE, n.d. (Box 28-30)